College english test band four part two
大学英语四级考试第二部分
Listening comprehension section a
听力理解 A节
Directions , in this section you will hear three news reports
说明：在本节中，你将听到三篇新闻报道
At the end of each news report
每篇新闻报道结束后
You will hear two or three questions
你将听到两到三个问题
Both the news report and the questions will be spoken only once
新闻报道和问题都只读一遍
After you hear a question
听完问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选出最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet one
然后在答题卡一上用横线划过相应字母
With a single line through the center
划一条线穿过中心
News report one
新闻报道一
a terrified cat has survived a five mile round trip
一只受惊的猫在一次五英里的往返旅程中幸存下来
Under the engine cover of a car on a school run
藏在一辆送学汽车引擎盖下
the black cat was found curled up under the engine cover of david king's car
当大卫·金决定检查机油时，发现这只黑猫蜷缩在他汽车的引擎盖下
when he decided to do an oil check
在肯特郡送孙子去学校后
After dropping his grandson off at school in kent
金先生的妻子说她丈夫跑进来
mr king's wife said her husband had come running in
大喊让我来看看
And was shouting for me to come have a look
我们甚至不确定它是否还活着
We weren't even sure it was alive
所以我用棍子轻轻推它检查它是否在呼吸
so i gently pushed it with a stick to check it was breathing
发现它是一只受惊的小猫
And saw it was a terrified little cat
它向引擎深处退去，被卡住了
It reversed even further into the engine and was stuck
我试图够到它，但它太深了
I tried to reach it but it was too far down
我无法把它弄出来
And there wasn't any way i could get it out
无论如何我都弄不出来
Anyway i could get it out
我能把它弄出来
Following a rescue by uk charity cats protection
在英国猫咪保护慈善机构的救援后
The four year old cat was later reunited with its owner , mr king's neighbor
这只四岁的猫后来与它的主人——金先生的邻居——团聚
Questions one and two are based on the news report you have just heard
问题一和问题二基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question one
问题一
where was the black cat found
这只黑猫是在哪里被发现的
question two
问题二
what do we learn about the cat at the end of the news report
新闻报道最后我们了解到关于这只猫的什么信息
News reports two in less than a month
新闻报道二 不到一个月内
The special olympic spring games will make a return to fayetteville
特殊奥林匹克春季运动会将重返费耶特维尔
The games are coming back for the first time in five years
这是五年来运动会首次回归
The events will take place at methodist university
活动将在卫理公会大学举行
Event organizer benjamin koalzac says
活动组织者本杰明·科尔扎克说
He's excited that athletes will get a chance to come back and demonstrate their abilities
他很兴奋运动员们有机会回来展示他们的能力
Organizers expect about a hundred athletes will come out to compete in fayetteville
组织者预计约一百名运动员将来到费耶特维尔参赛
They will have a variety of events to choose from
他们将有多种项目可供选择
Including running , throwing and jumping
包括跑步、投掷和跳跃
There will also be a fun ent for children
还将为孩子们设置一个娱乐帐篷
Koalzac said it's rewarding to see athletes with special needs triumph in the games
科尔扎克说看到有特殊需求的运动员在比赛中获胜是值得的
For anyone who wants to help make this year's games a massive success
任何想要帮助今年运动会取得巨大成功的人
There are still opportunities to volunteer for fayette vil's special olympics
费耶特维尔特殊奥林匹克运动会仍有志愿者机会
Organizers encourage them to visit the games website to sign up
组织者鼓励他们访问运动会网站报名
Questions three and four are based on the news report you have just heard
问题三和问题四基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question three
问题三
What will fait ville witness in less than a month
不到一个月后费耶特维尔将见证什么
question four
问题四
what did benjamin coalzac say is rewarding to see
本杰明·科尔扎克说什么是有回报的
News report three
新闻报道三
A german supermarket has been ordered to destroy its chocolate rabbits
一家德国超市被勒令销毁其巧克力兔子
After it lost a court battle with a swiss chocolate manufacturer
在与一家瑞士巧克力制造商的法庭诉讼中败诉后
the swiss firm had argued its gold wrapped chocolate rabbit
瑞士公司辩称其金箔包装的巧克力兔子
deserved copyright protection from a similar product
应该受到版权保护，免受类似产品的侵害
sold by the budget supermarket switzerland's highest court
由平价超市销售的瑞士最高法院
Agreed and overturned a ruling last year by the country's commercial court
同意并推翻了去年该国商业法院的裁决
That had sided with the supermarket
该裁决曾支持超市
It ordered that all the imitation rabbits be destroyed
法院下令销毁所有仿制兔子
But suggested the chocolate needn't be wasted
但建议巧克力不必浪费
It could be melted for use in other products
可以融化后用于其他产品
It said even though there are some differences between the two products
法院表示，尽管两种产品之间存在一些差异
There was still the possibility of confusion for consumers
消费者仍有可能产生混淆
The swiss manufacturers rabbit has a red bow and bell
瑞士制造商的兔子有红色蝴蝶结和铃铛
While the german supermarkets has a green bow and bell
而德国超市的有绿色蝴蝶结和铃铛
The color of the wrapper is similar
包装纸颜色相似
As are the illustrations of the features
特征插图也很相似
The chocolate company has been to court before to protect its popular chocolate treat
这家巧克力公司此前曾上法庭保护其受欢迎的巧克力产品
Last year , a german federal court said
去年，德国联邦法院表示
The shade of the gold wrapping was also protected
金色包装的色调也受到保护
Questions five to seven are based on the news report you have just heard
问题五至问题七基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question five
问题五
What has the german supermarket been ordered to do
德国超市被命令做什么
Question six
问题六
what did switzerland's highest court suggest about the chocolate in question
瑞士最高法院对涉案巧克力有什么建议
Questions seven
问题七
why did switzerland's highest court overturn the commercial courts ruling
为什么瑞士最高法院推翻了商业法院的裁决
Section b directions , in this section
B节说明：在本节中
You will hear two long conversations
你将听到两段长对话
At the end of each conversation
每段对话结束后
You will hear four questions
你将听到四个问题
Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once
对话和问题都只读一遍
After you hear a question
听完问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选出最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet one with a single line through the center
然后在答题卡一上用横线划过相应字母
Conversation one
对话一
Can you please hand me that book over there
你能把那边那本书递给我吗
It has instructions for making a winter bean salad
里面有制作冬季豆沙拉的说明
My sister's boyfriend is coming over for dinner
我姐姐的男朋友要来吃晚饭
He's vegetarian
他是素食主义者
So i need to make a lot of vegetable dishes
所以我需要做很多素菜
He only eats vegetables , no meat
他只吃蔬菜，不吃肉
That doesn't sound like a very balanced diet
这听起来不太像均衡饮食
How can he get enough protein
他怎么能获得足够的蛋白质
What does he do to strengthen his muscles and all that
他怎么增强肌肉之类的
Apparently that's . no problem
显然这不是问题
He's explained this to me when we first met
我们第一次见面时他就向我解释过
He eats a variety of different vegetables and nuts
他吃各种不同的蔬菜和坚果
Especially those with high amounts of protein
特别是那些蛋白质含量高的
It sounds a bit difficult
听起来有点困难
But he's done his research . i suppose
但我想他做过研究了
What's his reasoning for being vegetarian
他吃素的原因是什么
Is it his religion
是因为宗教吗
Health condition or lifestyle
健康状况还是生活方式
He's an animal activist
他是动物权益活动家
He's always been very sensitive and sympathizes with animals
他一直很敏感，对动物很有同情心
He's even written to his state senator about the torture of dolphins in separks
他甚至写信给州参议员，反映海豚在海洋公园受到的折磨
He says that keeping animals in zos and parks causes them great distress
他说把动物关在动物园和公园里会给它们带来巨大的痛苦
That's a little gloomy
这有点阴沉
But i can understand that to a point
但我能在某种程度上理解
Not all zos and animal parks have the most favorable conditions
并非所有动物园和动物公园都有最好的条件
But without them it just wouldn't be feasible to learn about animals and their environments
但如果没有它们，就不可能了解动物及其环境
Besides , i don't think i could ever give up a good hot dog at a baseball game
而且，我觉得我永远无法放弃棒球比赛上的美味热狗
Honestly , i agree
说实话，我同意
But just don't let him hear you say that he's the spokesperson for his local animal rights group
但别让他听到你这么说，他是当地动物权益组织的发言人
Questions eight to eleven are based on the conversation you have just heard
问题八至问题十一基于你刚才听到的对话
Question eight
问题八
What does the man request the woman to do
男士请求女士做什么
question nine
问题九
what does the woman say about eating vegetables only
女士对只吃蔬菜有什么看法
Question ten , why does the boyfriend of the man's sister
问题十：男士姐姐的男朋友
Choose to be a vegetarian
为什么选择成为素食主义者
question eleven on what point does the man agree with the woman at the end of the conversation
问题十一：对话结束时男士在什么观点上同意女士
Conversation two
对话二
Did you see that television program on air travel last night
你昨晚看那个关于航空旅行的电视节目了吗
Yes
看了
The part about overcoming jet lag was interesting
关于克服时差的部分很有趣
I was surprised that the expert recommended not eating for the
我很惊讶专家建议整个旅程中不要吃东西
Entire journey and avoiding sleeping on the plane
并且避免在飞机上睡觉
I was too , as i read an article on the subject in the past that suggested the opposite
我也很惊讶，因为我过去读过一篇关于这个主题的文章，建议恰恰相反
it claimed that it was important not to miss meals
文章声称不要错过用餐很重要
And that taking a nap on the plane
而且在飞机上小睡
Was the best way to adjust to a new time zone
是适应新时区的最好方法
Well , the expert on the show did cite research supporting her recommendations
节目中的专家确实引用了支持她建议的研究
So i guess i'll give it a try
所以我想我会试试
Next time i fly a long distance
下次我长途飞行时
Jet lag is a big problem for me
时差对我来说是个大问题
And has been for the last few years
过去几年一直如此
Even though i never suffered from it before
尽管我以前从未受过时差困扰
Well , she did say that jet lag often becomes more of a problem after forty
她说时差在四十岁以后往往会成为更大的问题
So i guess i'm lucky that i can still adjust to different time zones
所以我想我很幸运，我仍然可以适应不同的时区
Well , my problem is i'm afraid to fly
我的问题是我害怕坐飞机
Oh , i didn't know that actually
哦，我其实不知道
My mother is terrified of airplanes to the point where she can't even fly
我母亲对飞机恐惧到无法乘坐
So our family vacations were always by car or train
所以我们家的假期总是开车或坐火车
I'm not as bad as that
我没那么严重
I just get anxious before i fly
我只是在飞行前会焦虑
And feel nervous the whole time we're in the air
在空中的整个时间都会感到紧张
Which is why i was hoping the television program
所以我希望电视节目
Would cover that topic more than it did
能更多地讨论那个话题
Yeah , that segment was too brief
是的，那部分太简短了
Especially as so many people have that problem
尤其是因为那么多人有这个问题
She said twenty percent of people are afraid to fly
她说百分之二十的人害怕坐飞机
Actually it was a quarter of people
实际上是四分之一的人
So the problem really is widespread and deserves attention
所以这个问题确实很普遍，值得关注
Questions twelve to fifteen are based on the conversation you have just heard question twelve
问题十二至问题十五基于你刚才听到的对话 问题十二
What part of the tv program does the man say was interesting
男士说电视节目的哪部分很有趣
question thirteen
问题十三
what does the man say he will do next time he flies a long distance
男士说他下次长途飞行时会做什么
question fourteen
问题十四
Why does the woman think she is lucky
女士为什么觉得自己很幸运
question fifteen why does the woman think the problem of being afraid to fly deserves attention
问题十五：女士为什么认为害怕飞行的问题值得关注
Section c directions . in this section you will hear three passages
C节说明：在本节中，你将听到三篇短文
At the end of each passage
每篇短文结束后
You will hear three or four questions
你将听到三到四个问题
Both the passage and the questions will be spoken only once
短文和问题都只读一遍
After you hear a question
听完问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选出最佳答案
B , c , and d
B、C和D
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer
然后在答题卡
Sheet one with a single line through the center passage one
一上用横线划过相应字母 短文一
The most common question i asked always centers around
我最常被问到的问题总是围绕
How to get started in user experience design
如何进入用户体验设计领域
To which my response is always that nothing can substitute real world experience
我的回答始终是，没有什么可以替代真实世界的经验
Building the skills required of a user experience designer takes time
培养用户体验设计师所需的技能需要时间
Patience and commitment
耐心和投入
Higher education is a great way to equip yourself with some core skills
高等教育是让你掌握一些核心技能的好方法
But it will not prepare you for actual challenges
但它无法为你准备实际挑战
You'll face with clients work
你在客户工作中将面临的
In other words
换句话说
Being proficient with a design tool
熟练使用设计工具
And the few methods doesn't make you a user experience designer
和几种方法并不能让你成为用户体验设计师
There simply isn't a one size fits all process
根本不存在一刀切的流程
Being effective requires adaptability
有效工作需要适应能力
Something you don't really learn in school
这是你在学校里学不到的
Much less in a sixth month training camp
更不用说六个月的训练营了
It's gained through experience on the job
它是通过工作经验获得的
And learning what's appropriate given the needs of the project
并根据项目需求学习什么是合适的
i found my way to user experience through graphic design
我是通过平面设计进入用户体验领域的
And slowly over many
慢慢地经过多年
Different roles and experiences that led me to become a user experience designer
不同的角色和经历让我成为了一名用户体验设计师
it took time and commitment to continue to pursue
我花时间和精力继续追求
roles within teams that i knew could teach and challenge me
那些我知道可以教会我并挑战我的团队角色
That's not to say that i think my path is the only one
这并不是说我认为我的路是唯一的
But once again , nothing can substitute real world experience
但再一次强调，没有什么可以替代真实世界的经验
you can start anywhere as long as you know your end goal
只要你知道你的最终目标，你可以从任何地方开始
And you commit to actively pursuing opportunities to learn and grow along the way
并致力于积极寻找沿途学习和成长的机会
Questions sixteen to eighteen are based on the passage you have just heard
问题十六至问题十八基于你刚才听到的短文
Question sixteen
问题十六
What does the speaker think is the best way to get started in user experience design
演讲者认为进入用户体验设计领域最好的方式是什么
question seventeen what does the speakers say being effective requires
问题十七：演讲者说有效工作需要什么
question eighteen
问题十八
what can people do as long as they know their end goal and strive for it
只要人们知道自己的最终目标并为之努力，他们可以做什么
Passage two
短文二
When planning for this year
在为今年做计划时
Our principal asked what needed to change to engage students more in their learning
我们校长问需要改变什么才能让学生更多地参与学习
I responded in a whisper
我低声回答
Flexible seating
灵活座位
Thinking about our then current classroom
想到我们当时的教室
It had rows of desks with blue chairs and name plates
它有成排的桌子和蓝色椅子以及名牌
Reminding each student where they should be sitting
提醒每个学生他们应该坐在哪里
This began a journey to transform our practice
这开始了一段转变我们实践的旅程
And challenged the ways of learning
并挑战了学习方式
For a group of year six
对一群六年级学生来说
Students used to sitting in desks and rose for years
他们习惯于多年来坐在课桌和排座中
Flexible seating has been defined as movable furniture to create an engaging learning environment
灵活座位被定义为可移动家具，用于创造引人入胜的学习环境
It is a shift in practice from being teacher focused to student focused learning
这是一种从以教师为中心向以学生为中心学习的实践转变
For us
对我们来说
flexible seeding has meant removing most of the traditional chairs and desks
灵活座位意味着移除大部分传统椅子和桌子
And introducing a variety of different seeding options to promote student engagement
并引入各种不同的座位选择以促进学生参与
the use of rows and their minimal adaptations to you shape
排座及其对U形的微小改动
Were traditionally intended to maximize on task behavior
传统上旨在最大化任务行为
And reduce distraction from the teacher
并减少来自教师的干扰
teachers tend to still use this format
教师倾向于仍然使用这种格式
Because of either the need to control students
因为要么需要控制学生
Or the belief that the teacher is the most important person in the room
要么相信教师是房间里最重要的人
Now our students have a range of different seating options
现在我们的学生有各种不同的座位选择
Including a floor desk
包括地板桌
Couches , stools
沙发、凳子
Bean bags , and the traditional desk in chair
豆袋和传统的桌椅
From our experience so far
根据我们目前的经验
Flexible seeding enhances student ownership of space
灵活座位增强了学生对空间的主人感
An engagement in learning while reducing rates of student disengagement and disciplinary actions
和学习参与度，同时降低了学生脱离和纪律处分的比率
It is a win for all concerned
这对所有相关人员都是双赢
Questions nineteen to twenty one are based on the passage you have just heard
问题十九至问题二十一基于你刚才听到的短文
Question nineteen
问题十九
Why did the school principle ask what needed to change
校长为什么问需要改变什么
Question twenty
问题二十
What has flexible seating meant at the speaker's school
灵活座位在演讲者的学校意味着什么
Question twenty one
问题二十一
What has flexible seating brought about at the speaker's school
灵活座位给演讲者的学校带来了什么
Passage three
短文三
Dozens of british students arriving for their first day of school on tuesday
周二，数十名英国学生来到学校的第一天
Were sent home over their shoes
却因为鞋子问题被送回家
About thirty students were turned away from taverham high school in norfolk , england
大约三十名学生被英国诺福克郡塔弗纳姆高中拒之门外
Head teacher dr roger harris confirmed that this was due to a change in the school's uniform policy
校长罗杰·哈里斯博士证实，这是由于学校校服政策的变化
Harris
哈里斯
Who became head teacher this year
今年成为校长
Said he notified parents of the updated rules in an email in june
说他在六月份的一封电子邮件中通知家长更新后的规则
The price of school uniforms can spark panic among families
校服价格可能会在家庭中引发恐慌
Struggling with the high cost of living
那些正在应对高昂生活成本的家庭
Nearly all british schools have uniforms
几乎所有英国学校都有校服
They cost parent an average of three hundred
家长每年平均花费三百
And thirty seven pounds per year for each secondary school child
三十七英镑为每个中学校服
According to the new rules
根据新规定
Students of tavergham are required to wear smart black shoes appropriate for the workplace
塔弗纳姆的学生必须穿着适合工作场所的黑色正装鞋
Harris held that strengthened rules around school uniforms
哈里斯坚持认为加强校服规定
Improved student outcomes and behavior
改善了学生的成绩和行为
But for some parents
但对于一些家长来说
The school's restrictions are an unnecessary burden
学校的限制是不必要的负担
As annual inflation climbs over ten percent
随着年通货膨胀率超过百分之十
Many households are on tight budgets
许多家庭预算紧张
Private rental prices in britain
英国私人租赁价格
Rose three point two percent over the twelve months to july twenty twenty two
截至2022年7月的十二个月内上涨了百分之三点二
The largest jump since twenty sixteen
是自2016年以来的最大涨幅
Soaring energy bills have made things worse
飙升的能源账单使情况更加糟糕
Lucinda may
露辛达·梅
Mum of a tabraham student
一位塔弗纳姆学生的母亲
Said that she had to ask her parents for sixty five pounds to buy her child the correct pair of shoes
说她不得不向父母借六十五英镑给孩子买正确的鞋子
May said that the school's uniform policy show the lack of regard for parents dealing with the high cost of living
梅说学校的校服政策显示了对应对高昂生活成本的家长缺乏考虑
Questions twenty two to twenty five are based on the passage you have just heard
问题二十二至问题二十五基于你刚才听到的短文
Question twenty two
问题二十二
Why were dozens of british students sent home on tuesday
为什么周二几十名英国学生被送回家
Question twenty three
问题二十三
What can the price of school uniforms spark among families in financial difficulty
校服价格会在经济困难的家庭中引发什么
Question twenty four
问题二十四
What did the head teacher think of the school's new uniform rules
校长对学校的新校服规定有什么看法
Question twenty five
问题二十五
what did lucinda may have to do to buy her child the correct pair of shoes
露辛达·梅为了给孩子买正确的鞋子不得不做什么
that's the end of listening comprehension
听力理解部分结束